Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive MSS.091
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Material
  - Subseries C: Photographs
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9205 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Moving Tent, South Bronx, 1979; cuid9206 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Music, people & other objects, at exhibition of Haim Steinbach, 1980; cuid9207 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Neighborhood, mostly 3rd Ave. Betw. 135 and 165 St., Bronx, NY, undated; cuid9208 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Owens, Ashley., undated; cuid9209 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Pesce, Victor: "Water colors and drawin", February 28 - March 21, 1981., cuid9210 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Place, Chuck Hamilton: Spring 1982., cuid9211 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Polly Ester Nation: "Jesus comes to the Bronx", March 1980. [see also I. 1. 7], cuid9212 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Poppitz & Santos., undated; cuid9213 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Reccha, Louis., undated; cuid9214 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Riviera, James, undated; cuid9215 (Box 25, Folder 40A.)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS, 1985; cuid9216 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Rothschild, Gail: "Three Arches", October 6, 1984., cuid9217 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Sacchetto, Bruno:, 1980; cuid9218 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Schecter, Jill, undated; cuid9219 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Science and Technology Exhibition, 1982; cuid9220 (Box 25, Folder 44A.)
    - Sebrens, Sam:, 1986; cuid9221 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Schr, Beate Maria: "Bodysuits", 1993; cuid9222 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9223 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes:, 1985; cuid9224 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Spank., undated; cuid9225 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1980; cuid9226 (Box 25, Folder 49A)
    - Stout, Nancy., undated; cuid9227 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - South Bronx Show, 1979 (?); cuid9228 (Box 25, Folder 50A)
    - Taylor, David., undated; cuid9229 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Toral, Tabo [see also III. C. 6. 30], undated; cuid9230 (Box 25, Folder 51A.)
    - Vulva, by G. J. W., Fall 1992 [see also I. 1. 45], cuid9231 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Wells, David: "Cranach Cutouts", 1981, others, cuid9232 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified photographs., undated; cuid9233 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Subseries D: Artworks
    Series III Subseries D, Artworks, contains artworks by Keith Haring, Andre Charles, Daze, Crash, Kenny Scharf, Koor, and others. Included here is the Fashion Moda Portfolio with works by Ronnie Cutrone, Crash, Daze, Leon Golub, and James Poppitz.
    - Aone: drawings, incl. for Documenta 7. [see oversize, Box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9234 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Brasz, Marc: drawing., undated; cuid9235 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Charles, Andre: "South Bronx Show", 1988; cuid9236 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Cooney, Robert: "Por Exxon For Kill". [see over oversize, box 22], undated; cuid9237 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Crash: drawing for Documenta 7, other [see also oversize, box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9238 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Daze: drawing., undated; cuid9239 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Eins, Stefan. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9240 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Fekner, John: drawing for Documenta 7, others [see also oversize, box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9241 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - G-Man, drawing [see oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9242 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Haring, Keith; drawing for Documenta 7. [removed to oversize Box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9243 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Headley, Wendell: drawings, 1982; cuid9244 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Isaac: art for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9245 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Koor: drawing., undated; cuid9246 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Kostner, Arthur: drawings. [see over oversize, box 22], undated; cuid9247 (Box 26, Folder 13A.)
    - Mullican, Mat [see oversize box 21], undated; cuid9248 (Box 26, Folder 13B.)
    - Nenner, Paulette: drawing for Documenta 7 [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9249 (Box 26, Folder 14, Box 24)
    - Pabon, Jorge: drawing., undated; cuid9250 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Pou, Alyson: collage for Documenta 7 [removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9251 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Ramos: drawing., undated; cuid9252 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Satanic Show [see also I. 1. 21], undated; cuid9253 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Scharf, Kenny: drawing for Documenta 7. [removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9254 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Steckel, Anita: photograph for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9255 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Thomas, Kathleen: drawings., undated; cuid9256 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Toxic: drawing. [see oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9257 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified drawings. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9258 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - van Dalen, Anton: drawing for Documenta 7[removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9259 (Box 26, Folder 23A.)
    - Wells, David: drawings for Documenta 7. [removed to oversixe Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated; cuid9260 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Y-Pants, drawing, undated; cuid9261 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Fashion Moda Porfolio with works by Ronnie Cutrone, Crash, Daze, Leon Golub, and James Poppitz. (In Mapcase), undated; cuid9262 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Subseries E: Printed Materials
    Series III Subseries E, Printed Materials, contains magazines, journals, and catalogs on artists such as Mark Kostabi, Ron English, Nancy Stout, and Amy Chaiklin. These items were found in the collection and do not necessary pertain solely to Fashion Moda.
    - Art Com: number 16, v. 4 #4, 1982., cuid9263 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bomb: Spring/Summer 1985., cuid9264 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - The Bride Groom is Hear, 1976, cuid9265 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: "Wall-painting" book, 1983., cuid9266 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - [item removed]., undated; cuid9267 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - English, Ron: "Art is a Horrible Waste of the Imagination", 1988., cuid9268 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Events, New Museum: New York, 1981 [see also I. 1. 16], cuid9269 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9270 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Galleria Communale d'Arte Moderna, Bologna: "Arte di Frontera", March- April 1984., cuid9271 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Kostabi, Mark: catalog, 1986., cuid9272 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Mati et Mire, Isy Brachot, Paris: 1985., cuid9273 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Mickiemoda, Annie: "The Modamutations"., undated; cuid9274 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - New Observations, issue #71, October 1 - November 14, 1989., cuid9275 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - New Observations, issue #73, January 1 - February 14, 1990., cuid9276 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - New Observation, issue #75, April 1 - May 14, 1990., cuid9277 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Pflasterstrand, vom 31. 1 bis 13. 2. 1981, Germany., cuid9278 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Rammellzee: "Iconic Treatise Gothic Futurism... ", 1979, cuid9279 (Box 26, Folder 16A.)
    - Space Window, catalog, September 14 - October 6, 1997., cuid9280 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Stout, Nancy: "The Way We Were"., undated; cuid9281 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Unidentified printed materials., undated; cuid9282 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Virus, graffiti zine, Holland., undated; cuid9283 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Waxberg, Richard, undated; cuid9284 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Yarber, Robert, undated; cuid9285 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Subseries F[1]: Slides
    Box 7: 1978 - 1980
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9286 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Hill-Montgomery, Candance: installation, 1980; cuid9287 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9288 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Polly Ester Nation: "Jesus Comes to the Bronx", March 1980., cuid9289 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - May 1980., cuid9290 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Steinbach, Haim: Summer 1980., cuid9291 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Edwards, Marianne: Summer 1980., cuid9292 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Dickson, Jane: "City Maze", September 6 - October 4, 1980., cuid9293 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Sophie Calle, C. Ginsberg, November 25, 1980., cuid9294 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Cooper, Martha: Subwa, 1980; cuid9295 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Subseries F[2]: Slides
    Box 8: 1981 - 1983
    - Eyes and Ears Foundation, "California Billboards", 1980- 1981; cuid9296 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - California Billboards in New York, 1981; cuid9297 (Box 8, Folder 11A)
    - Pass, D.: "It's a Piece of Cake", 1980- 1981; cuid9298 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Yohai Andors, Rhoda: "Skeleton Paintings", February 6-28, 1981, cuid9299 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Optima Studio: New Orleans, Spring, 1981; cuid9300 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Pizzanello, Josephine, others, Fall 1981, cuid9301 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Graffiti: Summer 1981., cuid9302 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Contemporary Art Center, New Orleans: Summer 1981., cuid9303 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - South Bronx Art, Projects, Others: Summer 1981., cuid9304 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - de Mille, Arnette / Malca: Dance at opening of "South Bronx Art, Projects, Others", Summer 1981, cuid9305 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Larkin, Sara: "Scapes of Outer Space", September 1981., cuid9306 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - October 1981., cuid9307 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Pou, Alyson: "Measured Fantasies", November 1981., cuid9308 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Thomas, Kathleen: Fall 1981., cuid9309 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Wells, David: "Royal Hunt" and "Time Machine", Fall 1981., cuid9310 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Gutzeit, Fred: January 16 - February 17, 1982., cuid9311 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Spring Fever, March 1982, cuid9312 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Documenta 7: merchandise, May 1982. [No Duplication Allowed], cuid9313 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - South Bronx Show, Summer 1982., cuid9314 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Baca, Fred, Fekner, John and Leicht, Don: "From Monkey to Monitor", Fall 1982., cuid9315 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Graffiti Mural, 1983; cuid9316 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Haring, Keith: "Installation at Tony Shafrazi", 1983; cuid9317 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Golubovic, Vesna: Installation on E 146 St, Bronx, 1983; cuid9318 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Dragan Ilic: "Man with the Red Pencils", February 1983., cuid9319 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Seeno, Anson: "Watching", March 1983., cuid9320 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Fashion Moda Open House, July 23, 1983., cuid9321 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Pier 34, exhibition, Fall 1983., cuid9322 (Box 8, Folder 35a.)
    - Rheinberg, Raffael: September 1983., cuid9323 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Roloff, Stephen: "Paper Murals", September 25, 1983., cuid9324 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Collins, Marshall: "World of Dinosaurs", November - December 1983., cuid9325 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Daze, Keith Haring, Kenny Scharf, others: Mural at Houston and Bowery, NYC, 1983; cuid9326 (Box 8, Folder 38A)
  - Subseries F[3]: Slides
    Box 9: 1984
    - Touring Show, "Of the Streets", 1984 [see also I. 1. 34 and III. C. 6. 6 and III. B. oversize 21. 19-24], cuid9327 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Poppitz, James: tour and projects, 1983-1986; cuid9328 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Wahl, Anita: January 10 - February 8, 1984., cuid9329 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - [item removed]., undated; cuid9330 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Buggiani, Paolo: April 7-17, 1984., cuid9331 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Graupe-Pill, Grace:, 1984; cuid9332 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Cyphers, Peggy: "Modern Fossils", April 28, 1984., cuid9333 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Graffiti Masters Show: April 28 - May 19, 1984., cuid9334 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Niedzialek, Terry: July 1984., cuid9335 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - South Bronx Show: August 1984., cuid9336 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - South Bronx, ca. 1984, cuid9337 (Box 9, Folder 48A.)
    - Mulero, Lillian: "Real Politic", October 29 - November 16, 1984., cuid9338 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Lady Pink/Lady Heart: installation, November 1984., cuid9339 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Ellis, Darrel: "Drawings from my Father's Photographs", December 1984., cuid9340 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Edwards, Marianne:, 1984; cuid9341 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Subseries F[4]: Slides
    Box 10: 1985
    - A-One, Toxic, Koor:, 1985; cuid9342 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - P. S. 25: March, 1985; cuid9343 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Van II: March, 1985; cuid9344 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: March 9 - April 10, 1985., cuid9345 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Social Studies, Agent, Marc Brasz & James Rivera: April 20 - May 16, 1985., cuid9346 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Democracy at Work at 22 Wooster St.: May 31 - June 22, 1985., cuid9347 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Poppitz, James: Graffiti Desk at Fashion Moda, June 1985 [see also I. 1. 32]., cuid9348 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - South Bronx Show: June 15 - July 17, 1985., cuid9349 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Fiorucci: window displays, July 19 - August 1, 1985., cuid9350 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Expression African, September 1985., cuid9351 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Eins, Stefan: November 1985., cuid9352 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Fashion Moda Benefit at Ronald Feldman, Soho, November 1-16, 1985., cuid9353 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated; cuid9354 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Subseries F[5]: Slides
    Box 11: 1985 - 1986
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9355 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Robert Grahm/Susan Springfield: December 1985 - January 1986., 1985 - 1986; cuid9356 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Tim Rollins and the Kids of Survival: January - February 1986., cuid9357 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Stout, Nancy: march 1986., cuid9358 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Pod: facade of Fashion Moda, March 1986 [see also I. 1. 40], cuid9359 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Sacchetto, Bruce: March 1 - April 12, 1986., cuid9360 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Images in Fiber & Cloth: April 1986., cuid9361 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Lowinger, Leslie: May 7, 1986., cuid9362 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Moet and Delta: facade of Fashion Moda, June - July 1986. [see also I. 1. 40], cuid9363 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - South Bronx Show: June 21 - August 1, 1986., cuid9364 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Pieces Sold: June 1986., cuid9365 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9366 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Art for Money Benefit, December 1986, cuid9367 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Police Officers from local precinct: Installation, n. d., undated; cuid9368 (Box 11, Folder 78A)
  - Subseries F[6]: Slides
    Box 12: 1987 - 1993
    - Unidentified, 1986; cuid9369 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Unidentified exhibition, July 1987., cuid9370 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - South Bronx Show: 1987., cuid9371 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9372 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Corn, Thom: 1988., cuid9373 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Wibmer, Margret; March 29 - April 15, 1988., cuid9374 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Lens, Jessica: "The Sun, the Moon, and the Connected Stars... ", June 15-28, 1988., cuid9375 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Smith, Barbara: "Pageant of the Holy Squash", December 1988., cuid9376 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Back Room: January 1989., cuid9377 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - New location: January 1989, cuid9378 (Box 12, Folder 87A)
    - Toral, Tabo: facade of Fashion Moda, 1989; cuid9379 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Misera, Lisi: Installation, 1989; cuid9380 (Box 12, Folder 88A)
    - Unidentified Slides, undated; cuid9381 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Subseries F[7]: Slides
    Box 13: Individual Artists A-K.
    - Ahearn, John, undated; cuid9382 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Anderson, Laura, undated; cuid9383 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Applebroog, Ida., undated; cuid9384 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Beuys, Joseph, undated; cuid9385 (Box 13, Folder 94A.)
    - Bieber, Lorna., undated; cuid9386 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Brasz, Mark, undated; cuid9387 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Brown, Marion., undated; cuid9388 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Buggiani, Paolo, undated; cuid9389 (Box 13, Folder 97A)
    - Chaiklin, Amy., undated; cuid9390 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Charles, Andre., undated; cuid9391 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Cohen, Helen., undated; cuid9392 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Colescott, Robert., undated; cuid9393 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Collins, Marshall, undated; cuid9394 (Box 13, Folder 101A.)
    - Corn, Thom., undated; cuid9395 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Crash., undated; cuid9396 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Crawford, Lonnie & Cutrone., undated; cuid9397 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Daze., undated; cuid9398 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - de Preter, Jon., undated; cuid9399 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Dickson, Jane., undated; cuid9400 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Drew, Nancy, undated; cuid9401 (Box 13, Folder 107A.)
    - Eins, Stefan., undated; cuid9402 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - English, Ron., undated; cuid9403 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - [item removed]., undated; cuid9404 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Fekner, John., undated; cuid9405 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Finn, David., undated; cuid9406 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Freedom, undated; cuid9407 (Box 13, Folder 112A.)
    - Fun shots of Fashion Moda., undated; cuid9408 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Futura 2000, undated; cuid9409 (Box 13, Folder 113A)
    - Gadea, Patricia., undated; cuid9410 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Hambleton, Richard., undated; cuid9411 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Haring, Keith., undated; cuid9412 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - Harris, Tim., undated; cuid9413 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Headley, Wendell., undated; cuid9414 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Hertz, Betti-Sue., undated; cuid9415 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Hill-Montgomery, Candace., undated; cuid9416 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Hoffman, Wendy., undated; cuid9417 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Ilic, Dragan, undated; cuid9418 (Box 13, Folder 121A.)
    - Jordan, Ariel Orr., undated; cuid9419 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Jones, Kim, undated; cuid9420 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Kostabi, Mark., undated; cuid9421 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Ladda, Justen., undated; cuid9422 (Box 13, Folder 124A.)
  - Subseries F[8]: Slides
    Box 14: Individual Artists L-Z
    - Quinones, Lee, undated; cuid9423 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - Lewis, Joe., undated; cuid9424 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - Lowinger, Leslie., undated; cuid9425 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - Mann, Frank, undated; cuid9426 (Box 14, Folder 127A.)
    - Nadel, Jeremy., undated; cuid9427 (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - Neal, Willie, undated; cuid9428 (Box 14, Folder 128A.)
    - Paddock, Laura, undated; cuid9429 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - Pink, Lady, undated; cuid9430 (Box 14, Folder 129A.)
    - Quinn, Barbara., undated; cuid9431 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - Reccha, Lewis., undated; cuid9432 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - Rivera, James., undated; cuid9433 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - Rifka, Judy, undated; cuid9434 (Box 14, Folder 132A.)
    - Roloff, Stephan., undated; cuid9435 (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - Rothchild, Gail., undated; cuid9436 (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - Schlefer, R., undated; cuid9437 (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - Schwartz, Steve, undated; cuid9438 (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - Seeno, Anson, undated; cuid9439 (Box 14, Folder 136A.)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes, undated; cuid9440 (Box 14, Folder 136B.)
    - Spero, Nancy., undated; cuid9441 (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Steckel, Anita, undated; cuid9442 (Box 14, Folder 137A.)
    - Strauss, Sandy., undated; cuid9443 (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Street Art, undated; cuid9444 (Box 14, Folder 138A.)
    - Spank., undated; cuid9445 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - Sumner, Holly & Talbot, Nina., undated; cuid9446 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Toral, Tabo., undated; cuid9447 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Transue, Michael., undated; cuid9448 (Box 14, Folder 141A.)
    - Tuck, Norman., undated; cuid9449 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Unidentified artists, undated; cuid9450 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Various., undated; cuid9451 (Box 14, Folder 143A)
    - Warren, Tom, undated; cuid9452 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Weeks, Lionel "Agent", undated; cuid9453 (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Wodiczko, Krysztof., undated; cuid9454 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Wosk, Miriam., undated; cuid9455 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - undated, cuid9456 (Box 14, Folder .)
  - Subseries F[9]: Slides
    Box 15: Slide Presentation
    - Fashion Moda Slide Show: with explanation sheet (ca 1990), an introductory overview, including certain duplicates, cuid9457 (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - Subseries G: Video - Access Copies
    Consists of VHS access copies for Stephan Eins' Making Coincidences and other cable TV programs. Access copies are listed chronologically.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Cable TV 1 - Josef, circa mid-1970s; ID: 091.0071 (Case 091.0071)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:29:00.
    - Cable TV 2 - Leanne, circa mid-1970s; ID: 091.0073 (Case 091.0073)
    - Cable TV 3 - Terry & Wendy, circa mid-1970s; ID: 091.0075 (Case 091.0075)
    - Cable TV 4 - Alone, circa mid-1970s; ID: 091.0078 (Case 091.0078)
      Format: DVD
      Duration: 00:29:00
    - "Grafitti" Dub; CBS "30-Minutes", undated; ID: 091.0081 (Case 091.0081)
      Duration: 00:14:00
    - Making Coincidences, February 5, 1984., ID: 091.0033 (Case 091.0033)
    - Making Coincidences, February 12, 1984, ID: 091.0035 (Case 091.0035)
    - Making Coincidences, February 19, 1984, ID: 091.0037 (Case 091.0037)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:30:00.
    - Making Coincidences, February 26, 1984, ID: 091.0039 (Case 091.0039)
    - Making Coincidences, March 4, 1984, ID: 091.0041 (Case 091.0041)
    - Making Coincidences, March 18, 1984, ID: 091.0043 (Case 091.0043)
    - Making Coincidences, March 25, 1984, ID: 091.0045 (Case 091.0045)
    - Making Coincidences, April 1, 1984, ID: 091.0047 (Case 091.0047)
    - Making Coincidences, April 8, 1984, ID: 091.0049 (Case 091.0049)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:28:00.
    - Making Coincidences, April 15, 1984 (as per cassette)/April 22, 1984 (as per container), ID: 091.0051 (Case 091.0051)
    - Making Coincidences, April 29 & May 6, 1984, ID: 091.0053 (Case 091.0053)
    - Making Coincidences, May 13, 1984, ID: 091.0055 (Case 091.0055)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984, ID: 091.0057 (Case 091.0057)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984, ID: 091.0059 (Case 091.0059)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:07:00.
    - Making Coincidences, June 3, 1984, ID: 091.0061 (Case 091.0061)
    - Making Coincidences, X. Y. C., 1984; ID: 091.0063 (Case 091.0063)
    - Slow Scan: March, 1979, ID: 091.0084 (Case 091.0084)
      Duration: 00:22:00
    - Stefan Eins Presents: July 11 and 21, 1986, ID: 091.0065 (Case 091.0065)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: 2/25/1987, ID: 091.0067 (Case 091.0067)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. Duration: 00:47:00.
    - Stefan Eins Presents: edit in process, March 25, 1987, ID: 091.0069 (Case 091.0069)
  - Subseries H: Video - Originals
    Consists of original source tapes for Stephan Eins' Making Coincidences and other cable TV programs. Materials are listed chronologically. For access copies please see Subseries G.
    - Press for Making Coincidences, title cards for show. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9458 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Cable TV-1-Josef, n. d., circa mid-1970s; cuid9459 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0021)
      3/4" Umatic videocassette. Tape length 30 minutes.
    - Cable TV -2-Leanne, n. d., circa mid-1970s; cuid9460 (Box 18, Folder ID: 091.0022)
    - Cable TV -3-Terry & Wendy, n. d., circa mid-1970s; cuid9461 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0023)
    - Cable TV -4-Alone, n. d., circa mid-1970s; cuid9462 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0024)
    - [1.] -- Slow Scan Tele Conference [2.] -- Manhattan/Bronx; 3/6/1979 and 3/7/1979., cuid9463 (Box 19, Folder ID: 091.0029)